[Music]
in this release we expanded amount of
information which Shopify and Business
Center Exchange in B2B scenario Shopify
connector now Imports all location all
Company locations and also includes
payment terms and tax ID information the
tax ID information can be used for
automatic entity mapping now when export
data from business Central to Shopify
customer to company we also include tax
ID and Company ID that also improves
order creation and
traceability automatic creation of
cataloges ensures that prices are equal
between Shopify and business Central
let's see it in action Shopify company
can have multiple locations with
different addresses tax IDs and payment
terms the Shopify connector now Imports
all locations into business Central
report the company from
Shopify now explore the entity to see
the populated tax
ID choose the Shopify locations action
to view the list of locations there are
two entries showing address information
tax and payment term codes the default
entry is used as the main source when
creating or updating customer cards
since it is impossible to specify in the
Shopify admin which location is default
the connector uses the first
one the company was mapped to customer
using the registration no based on
Shopify Shop Card
settings the change log shows that
payment terms were also updated it is
important to map Shopify payment terms
to business central payment
terms all right we so import works now
it's time to explore export of the data
export a customer as a Shopify
company notice the tax ID the new
company Tax ID mapping field on the
Shopify shop car page lets you choose to
send either the registration number or
the vat registration number as the tax
ID if you configured the Shopify
connector to create a catalog the
customer number field is now filled in
in for the catalog this enhancement
ensures that the connector uses the
specific customer to calculate prices
eliminating the need to fill in other
fields you just need to turn on the sync
prices toggle and select sync prices to
start synchronizing catalog
prices in created Shopify Company the
company ID is filled in with the
customer number which enhances
tracability
if payment terms mapping is configured
the payment term details transfer to
Shopify and are stored in the default
company
location also the Shopify connector
fills in the company/ attention field in
the created company location with a
company name the name is used in
imported orders thank you for watching
you can find additional details about
this capability in the release notes
also check other videos about Shopify
connector enhancements you can find
links in the description